Julissa Zavala

UX DESIGNER

Product designer specializing in UX Design with 4+ years of prior experience in non-profit work centered on youth development and education. My experience in education makes me a motivated individual with an empathetic mindset ready to develop creative solutions.

EDUCATION

DesignLab UX Certification

Expected Graduation May 2021

- 480 hour bootcamp to develop UX/UI design skills and training
- Diversify Design program full-ride scholarship recipient

B.A. in Child Study & Human Development

Tufts University 2016

SKILLS

- User Research
- Content Strategy
- Interaction Design
- Information Architecture
- Wireframing
- Rapid Prototyping
- Usability Testing
- Logo Design
- Visual Design

TOOLS

- Sketch
- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Illustrator
- Invision
- Webflow
- Zeplin
- HTML & CSS

EXPERIENCE

Freelance UX designer

November 2020 - Present

- Working with clients to design their website experiences

Advertising Market Research Specialist

Research Insights | October 2019 - November 2020

- Managed market research initiatives to gather feedback on industry trends, market needs, and pain points
- Sourced and screened potential survey participants
- Tracked and measured marketing outcomes

College Services Advisor

The Steppingstone Foundation | May 2018 - September 2020

- Executed coordination across departments for 10 program events including conferences and workshops for students and families
- Forged and maintained partnerships with high schools, colleges and outside organizations
- Designed marketing materials for program events

Teen Arts Specialist

The Steppingstone Foundation | May 2018 - September 2020

- Surpassed recruitment efforts for middle school youth in the Boston Area, generating 300% increase in applications for the Eliot School's Teen Bridge Program
- Communicated Artist-in-Residence progress to the Director of School & Community Partnerships
- Drafted contracts for 2018- 2019 Artists-in-Residence